{
  "Q&A": {
    "qa1": {
      "answer": "c",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa2": {
      "answer": "java",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa3": {
      "answer": "csharp",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa4": {
      "answer": "python",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language"
    },
    "qa5": {
      "answer": "javascript",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa6": {
      "answer": "dart",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa7": {
      "answer": "r",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa8": {
      "answer": "php",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa9": {
      "answer": "kotlin",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa10": {
      "answer": "ruby",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa11": {
      "answer": "typescript",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    },
    "qa12": {
      "answer": "golang",
      "question": "Guess the Programming Language ?"
    }
  }
}